hi I'm gonna giving you a peek at J
嗨，我要向您介绍J
shell which is the new interactive shell
shell是新的交互式shell
for the Java language in JDK 9
JDK 9中的Java语言
I'm Robert field I'm the architect and
我是罗伯特·菲尔德，我是建筑师，
lead of J shell so if you ever wondered
J Shell的负责人，如果您想知道
about some aspect about it of how Java
关于Java的某些方面
works the library a Java construct a bit
使用Java构建该库
of semantics
语义学
maybe you've written a little program to
也许你写了一个小程序来
find out let's say you don't know how
找出让我们说你不知道如何
unsigned shift works with negative
无符号移位负
numbers thing and read there but you
数字的东西，在那里读，但你
need to write a program so you create a
需要编写一个程序，以便您创建一个
file maybe in your IDE maybe from the
文件，也许在您的IDE中，可能来自
shell and you have to create a class and
外壳，您必须创建一个类并
a method public static void main and
一个方法public static void main和
arguments and a print line and then you
参数和打印行，然后您
can actually look at what you're
可以看你到底是什么
interested in well once you've done that
做完之后对好感
you need to compile it and then run it
您需要先编译然后运行
then you get an answer and that you
然后你得到一个答案，你
probably want to revise so let me show
可能想修改，让我展示
you how it's done in J shell in JCL we
您如何在JCL的J Shell中完成操作
can just type in what we're interested
可以输入我们感兴趣的内容
in and we immediately see the results
进入，我们立即看到结果
it's 1 and it's also put in a scratch
它是1，也被划掉了
variable called dollar one so we can
称为美元一的变量，因此我们可以
access it later if that's interesting to
如果感兴趣的话可以稍后访问
us but one doesn't tell me much what if
我们，但没有告诉我如果
it was minus three okay seven mean it
现在是负三好七是
looks like maybe bits let's find out by
看起来也许让我们找出
looking at a variety of value so we want
着眼于各种价值，所以我们想要
I to be let's say go up to minus 40 and
我可以说上升到负40
let's print out both the shift amount
让我们打印两个移位量
which is I and the result so the shift
这是我和结果，所以转移
amount is I the result is minus 1
金额是我，结果是负1
shifted by I and we see that all those
由我转移，我们看到所有这些
but those are bit so probably not a very
但那些可能不是那么非常
useful way to see how that works let's
看看它如何工作的有用方法
represent them as a bit so I know that
代表他们一点，所以我知道
integer has a function method that
整数有一个函数方法
converts to a bit string but I don't
转换为一点字符串，但我没有
know what it is so I can type tab here
知道这是什么，所以我可以在这里输入tab
and it will show me
它会告诉我
what methods there are on the integer
整数上有什么方法
class and sure enough there's a two
课，肯定有两个
binary string I put in to be and
我放入的二进制字符串是和
complete it and there we go well if you
完成它，我们可以顺利进行，如果您
make a mistake you immediately see it in
犯了一个错误，您会立即看到它
J shell in this case it's telling us
在这种情况下，J shell告诉我们
that it's now a string and we can't use
现在它是一个字符串，我们不能使用
an integer conversion for that so I have
为此，我有一个整数转换
to go back and change that to a string
返回并将其更改为字符串
and let's give a width to the other now
让我们现在给另一个宽度
let's look okay I only put in 20 spaces
好吧，我只放20个空格
and it's a 32-bit integer let's really
这是一个32位整数
look at it it's the right width so we
看看它是正确的宽度，所以我们
can immediately play and and get exactly
可以立即播放并获得准确
the information we want okay now we're
现在我们想要的信息就可以了
going back to the slides what is Jason
回到幻灯片上，杰森是什么
child good for it's for exploring API is
对探索API有好处的孩子是
that are unfamiliar to you or language
不熟悉您或语言的人
features we just saw an example of that
功能，我们刚刚看到了一个例子
you get to experiment and instantly see
您开始实验并立即看到
results when you're new to job or new to
刚上班或刚上班时的结果
programming it every API and language
对每种API和语言进行编程
features a new to you so it's a great
为您提供了新功能，这很棒
way to learn you can start with
学习方式可以从
expressions and statements rather than
表达式和语句，而不是
having to understand the whole structure
必须了解整个结构
of a class and methods
类和方法
you also get immediate feedback which
您还会立即收到反馈
helps with learning and the third kind
帮助学习和第三种
of use of J shell is your prototyping
使用J shell是您的原型
something complex that you don't know
你不知道的复杂事物
exactly how it works you can do that bit
确切的工作原理，你可以做到这一点
at a time and build it up within J shell
一次并在J shell中建立它
but what it is J shell so it's a tool
但是它是J shell，所以它是一个工具
for dynamically interacting with the
用于与
java language it's a reader valuate
Java语言，是读者的评价
print loop or repple and finally there's
打印循环或重复，最后有
one for the java language you just type
一种用于您刚刚输入的Java语言
in a snippet of code and you see the
在一段代码中，您会看到
results so J shell is deeply integrated
结果，因此J Shell被深度集成
with the JDK toolset what that means is
使用JDK工具集意味着
it stays current and it's compatible
它保持最新并且兼容
with the language and semantics of Java
Java的语言和语义
so what we're looking at is going to be
所以我们要看的是
the tool because that's easy to show but
该工具，因为它很容易显示，但是
there's also an API on which JJ shell
还有一个JJ shell的API
tool is built and which you can build
工具已构建，您可以构建
another repple
另一个涟漪
choosing or use it with another tools
选择或与其他工具一起使用
that you want to be able to evaluate
您想要能够评估的
Java Java code how do you use the J
Java Java代码如何使用J
shell tool as we saw you just type in J
我们看到的shell工具，只需输入J
shell at the command line
命令行中的shell
assuming jdk nine is installed J shell
假设JDK安装了九个J Shell
tool uses two kinds of input one snippet
工具使用两种输入方式的一小段
so we've seen those little pieces of
所以我们已经看到了
declarations or execution I have the
声明或执行我有
other thing is J shell commands and they
另一件事是J Shell命令，它们
give you more information about what's
给您更多有关什么的信息
going on or allow you to control how J
进行或允许您控制J
Saltworks
盐场
commands are distinguished from snippets
命令与代码片段区分开
by using slash in front of them and your
通过在他们和你前面使用斜线
input whether it's snippets or commands
输入代码段或命令
can be tab completed and has a history
可以完成标签并具有历史记录
and and it can be edited the line
并且可以编辑该行
editing in fact uses Emacs standard
编辑实际上使用Emacs标准
Emacs bindings what are snippets their
Emacs绑定是什么片段
declarations which include variable
包含变量的声明
declarations method declarations class
声明方法声明类
declaration interfaces imports or
声明接口导入或
expressions from the very simple to
表达式从非常简单到
convoluted stream lambda expressions
卷积流lambda表达式
they're all the statements while if
他们都是陈述，而如果
switch so forth in fact the only things
切换实际上是唯一的事情
that aren't allowed are things that
不允许的是
don't make any sense in the context of J
在J的上下文中没有任何意义
shell not programming in the large so
外壳不大所以编程
there's no packages you can't have
没有你不能拥有的包裹
statements without their enclosing
不包含它们的声明
contacts just like you can't in
就像你不能进入
programming Java they're all more give
编程Java他们全都付出
you a little idea of the commands so
你对命令有点了解
there's commands to get information you
有命令来获取您的信息
can list the snippets you've entered you
可以列出您输入的摘录
can look at your variables etc eCourse
可以查看您的变量等eCourse
can exit J shell and you can set up an
可以退出J Shell，然后可以设置一个
environment you want to work in so you
您想要工作的环境，以便您
set your class pass module path you can
设置您的类传递模块路径
look at and access the history and you
查看并访问历史记录，您
can use any editor you want from within
可以从内部使用任何想要的编辑器
J shell you can also save your work and
您还可以使用J shell保存您的工作并
J shell is highly configurable so
J Shell高度可配置，因此
there's a sophisticated set command it
有一个复杂的set命令
allows you to set up J shell to work
允许您设置J shell进行工作
exactly
究竟
you want there's also online help for
您还希望获得在线帮助
all of all of this okay here's a quick
所有这些都很好，这是一个快速
look at the architecture of J shell
看一下J Shell的体系结构
don't need to worry about this too much
不用太担心这个
but I mentioned that it is built on top
但我提到它是建立在最上面的
of the JDK and sure enough it uses the
JDK并确定它使用了
standard Java C compiler and for
标准Java C编译器以及
execution it uses the standard virtual
执行它使用标准虚拟
machine between the J shell tool and the
J Shell工具与
J shell core implementation you see
您看到的J Shell核心实现
something called the J shell API that
称为J Shell API的东西
allows you to build other tools using
允许您使用构建其他工具
this functionality so let's play with
这个功能，让我们一起玩
that here's J shell I know that happens
我知道这是J shell
to be the core class of J shell but not
成为J shell的核心类，但不是
much else about it so we'll need to
还有很多其他的事情，所以我们需要
import that there's a there's a cool
导入那里有一个很酷
trick in J shell you just say shift tab
J Shell中的技巧，您只需要说一下shift键
eye and it offers to import that class
眼睛，并提供导入该类
so we'll type one and it's now imported
所以我们将输入一个，然后将其导入
but I don't know what to do with this J
但我不知道该怎么办
shell class I've got let's hit tab and
我得到的shell类让我们点击Tab
see what the completions are well
看看完成得如何
creating an instance of J shell is what
创建一个J Shell实例是什么
I want so that sounds like the place to
我想要，这听起来像是
go now I want to hold on to that as well
现在走，我也想坚持下去
so let's hold on to our instance of J
因此，让我们坚持我们的J实例
shell by creating a variable by typing
通过键入一个变量来创建shell
shift tab V then I can all I have to do
转移Tab V然后我就可以做
is type in the name because it's already
输入名称，因为它已经
provided the type so I have the instance
提供了类型，所以我有实例
of J shell but I'm not quite sure what
J Shell的功能，但我不确定
to do with it
与之相关
we're gonna want to evaluate snippets
我们将要评估片段
let's see well look there's an eval
让我们一起看一下
method I have type you know fill in the
我知道你要输入的方法
eval but I don't know what the
评估，但我不知道
parameters are if I type tab again it
参数是如果我再次输入制表符
will actually show me what the
实际上会告诉我
parameters are it looks like it's a
参数看起来像是
string input but if I want more
字符串输入，但是如果我想要更多
information about what that is I can
关于我可以做什么的信息
type tab again it will give me the
再次键入选项卡，它将给我
documentation for eval okay let's say we
评估文档，好吧，我们说
want to just create a
只想创建一个
variable that's our test snippet for our
变量就是我们的测试代码段
new repple and we'll want to put that
新的奶嘴，我们要放
somewhere too so again let's type
还是在某个地方，让我们再次输入
shift-tab V and that's our result and
Shift-tab V，这就是我们的结果，
our result is a list of snippet events
我们的结果是摘要事件列表
and there's only one thing in that list
那只只有一件事
so let's get the one snippet event in
因此，让我们获得一个摘要事件
the list which we can do with get 0 I'm
我们可以做的清单是0
cheating and we want to hold on to that
作弊，我们要坚持下去
event - and saying not only can create a
事件-说不仅可以创建一个
variable we can also import that type
变量，我们也可以导入该类型
and create the variable which sounds
并创建听起来的变量
more elegant so let's do that let's call
更优雅，让我们打电话
that variable event now what can I do
那个可变事件我该怎么办
wanna vent looks like I have a lot of
想发泄看起来我有很多
options everything from the snippet that
从片段中选择所有内容
caused the event status and so forth and
导致事件状态等等
make an exception bolla see what our
例外bolla看看我们的
status is status is valid well that's
状态是状态有效，那是
good it's a valid snippet but what we're
好的，这是一个有效的代码段，但我们
really interested in is the value values
真正感兴趣的是价值
3 that sounds good too well now we're
3听起来太好了，现在我们
ready we can write a little method since
准备好我们可以写一个小方法，因为
we can write methods classes any of
我们可以编写任何方法类
those things in J shell and notice all
J Shell中的那些东西，并注意所有
along I'm using tab to complete things
我正在使用选项卡来完成事情
make this quick because I'm absolutely
快点说吧，因为我绝对
now what we want to do here is print out
现在我们要在这里做的是打印出来
the value so the value the value is a
值，所以值是
string and it's in we just saw is in the
字符串，它在我们刚才看到的在
value method and that's the end of our
价值方法，这就是我们的目的
method and so we've declared a method in
方法，因此我们在中声明了一个方法
J shell let's test it out so we can test
J Shell让我们对其进行测试，以便我们可以进行测试
immediately that's one of the designers
立即是设计师之一
of what you can do in J shell so we'll
您可以在J shell中执行的操作
display the event we just created
显示我们刚刚创建的事件
sure enough it gives us a value now we
足够肯定它给我们带来了价值
can write the first step in processing
可以写出处理的第一步
so the input we're going to process is a
所以我们要处理的输入是
string which is our snippet and we'll
字符串，这是我们的代码段，我们将
use that display method we just created
使用我们刚创建的显示方法
but what we're going to be displaying is
但是我们要显示的是
the evaluation what we saw before of
我们之前看到的评估
whatever the input was and again we're
无论输入什么，我们再次
gonna cheat and get the first result and
要作弊并得到第一个结果
now let's see what we've got
现在让我们看看我们有什么
can we process an input let's say can we
我们可以处理输入吗？可以
top process two plus two as an
顶部处理两个加两个作为
expression sure enough it works so where
表达足够肯定，所以在哪里
do you get all this J shell is part of
你得到所有这J外壳的一部分吗
JDK 9 which you can download at this
您可以在此处下载的JDK 9
link and please participate in our
链接，请参加我们的
mailing lists and follow us on Twitter
邮件列表，并在Twitter上关注我们
thank you
谢谢